ourdeal.com.au 2015-06-22

# OurDeal: Terms and Conditions

* * *

**Last updated on 14th February 2014**

**1.** This privacy policy is published by OurDeal Pty Ltd (ACN 136 842 745) (" **we/us/our** "). Our contact details are: Our Deal Privacy Officer, Level 2, 299 Elizabeth Street, Sydney NSW 2000; Phone: (02) 8305 1800; or email: [support@ourdeal.com.au](mailto:support@ourdeal.com.au). Our Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through our services including Deal advertising services, websites, mobile sites, and applications (" **apps** "). 

**2.** Definitions used in this privacy policy: 

  1. " **Partners** " means our associated entities (as defined in the Corporations Act 2001) and News Limited and Network Ten Pty Ltd and their associated entities.
  2. " **Platforms** " means our website and other e-commerce technology including apps and mobile telephone platforms.
  3. " **Suppliers** " means the third-party merchants who engage us to advertise their goods/services.

## Access to your personal information

**3.** You may ask us to provide you with access to the personal information that we hold about you unless there is an exception which applies under the Privacy Act. We will deal with any request from you to obtain access to your personal information within a reasonable time. If we refuse to provide you with access to your personal information, we will provide you with reasons for the refusal. 

**4.** If you wish to gain access to your personal information or if you have any questions about what sort of personal information we hold and for what purposes and how we collect, hold, use and disclose that information, please contact our Privacy Officer. 

**5.** We will take reasonable steps to correct any of your personal information that you can establish is not accurate, complete, up-to-date or relevant. 

**6.** You may ask us to remove your personal information from our database. 

## How we collect personal information

**7.** We will, in general, collect your personal information directly from you. For example, we may collect your personal information when you deal with us over the telephone, send us correspondence (including letters, faxes and emails or via our Platforms) and when you join OurDeal as a member/subscriber and when you purchase a Deal. Generally, the type of personal information that we collect includes your name, mailing address and postcode, telephone number/s and email address, date of birth and gender. Where the terms of a Deal do not require a voucher to be redeemed, we will also collect your nominated delivery address. 

**8.** We also use a range of social media channels such as Facebook and Twitter (" **social media** ") to distribute news, announcements, promotions, Deals and to address community enquiries If you submit or post comments, images, tweets, recordings or other personal content for public display on social media, that information may be available for anyone in the world to read/view/comment on. We encourage you to read the separate social media privacy policyies which relates to their use. We are not responsible to you for the information handling practices of social media. 

**9.** If you access or log in to our services via social media or connect our services to social media, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with the social media, any information or content you have elected to share on the social media with us, such as your name, age, date of birth, gender, profile picture, email address, followers or friends lists and any other information which you have disclosed or posted in connection with that social media. We do not collect your passwords except in relation to our own services. When you access our services through social media or when you connect our services to social media, you are authorising us to collect, store and use that information and content in accordance with this privacy policy. 

**10.** When you use and interact with our Platforms, we may collect certain information about your use. For example, our servers may log details about any computer that you use to access our website and we log behavioural data about you in relation to what Deals you have purchased. In addition, our website may store cookies on the web browser of your computer in order to better serve you upon subsequent visits to our Website. Cookies are data that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. Cookies allow us to track usage patterns and compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. The types of information that cookies can collect includes information about your computer, device, browser, potentially your IP address, and other software or hardware. 

If you use our Platforms from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier, geolocation data and other transactional information from that device. 

Other types of tracking technologies include pixels, beacons and Adobe Flash technology. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your use of our services, such as webpages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries that you have run and advertisements that you have seen. 

**11.** We may not always collect your personal information directly from you. Sometimes we collect your personal information from: 

  1. your personal acquaintances and friends through our "Refer a Friend" promotion of our services via our Platforms and if you are the recipient of an OurDeal gift card. Information collected from your acquaintances and friends through our "Refer a Friend" promotion and for gift cards is limited to your email address;
  2. our Partners, where you have given our Partners your express consent to provide your personal information to us.

## How we use personal information

**12.** We collect and use your personal information for the following primary purposes: 

  1. the supply of our services – which includes advertising Supplier's goods and services through Deals and selling vouchers to you on their behalf;
  2. to give Suppliers your name, voucher details and if applicable to a Deal, your nominated delivery address;
  3. to measure and improve our services and our Platforms. That includes improving your experience with our online and off-line services by delivering content to you that we believe you are likely to find relevant and interesting. It may also include using your information for research and data analysis by us and our service providers.
  4. communicating with you in connection with your Member account information and customer service issues;
  5. internal management and administrative purposes; and
  6. marketing of OurDeal and other promotional purposes in connection with our services. That includes advertising and marketing messages (which may include the display of personalised content and advertising) and to participate in competitions. Competitions are conducted by our business partners and are subject to their privacy policies.

**13.** The main consequences if all or some of your personal information is not collected, is that you may not be able to purchase Deals from us, or enjoy the benefits of our other services. 

**14.** We may also disclose your personal information to third party service and content providers that we engage to help us to help us provide and manage our services including to process payments, website hosting service providers, data cloud services, electronic communication providers and data analysis. We take reasonable steps that your personal information is only used for the services/purposes we require. 

Our Partners, third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and tracking technologies via our Platforms to obtain information such as demographic information, interests and your web activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. We may also do this. 

These third party service and content providers may be located in a range of different countries including the United Kingdom and United State of America. We generally require that these service and content providers comply with relevant privacy laws and do not use the personal information which we provide for any purpose other than the specific services they are providing to you and/or us. 

**15.** If you log in with or connect a social media account with our services, we may share your user name, picture, tweets, likes and preferences, as well as any other of your activities and comments, with other users of our services, and your friends who are linked to your social media account and with the social media provider. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, you should not connect your social media account with our services and you should not participate in social media sharing of your information. 

**16.** Whilst we stipulate in our contracts with Suppliers that your personal information cannot be used for any purpose other than the supply of their goods / services to you or as specifically set out in the Deal terms, we cannot guarantee that a Supplier will not use your personal information for any other purpose. 

**17.** We may also disclose your personal information to Suppliers for other purposes, for example competitions and promotions run by the relevant Supplier. However we will only do this if disclosed in the specific Deal Terms and you place an order for the Deal. 

**18.** We may share your personal information with our Partners. We, or they may also, (in addition to any of the other uses described in this policy or permitted at law), use your personal information to assist us and our Partners to communicate with you (via any form of media) in relation to our goods, services and promotions and to also display personalised content and advertising to you through sharing information collected through the use of cookies and other tracking technologies referred to above. 

**19.** We may also share your personal information with third parties with whom we run joint promotions or contract with to provide co-branded services. For example, we may contract with a shopping centre to advertise Deals by the merchants who trade in that shopping centre. The third party's use of your information will be governed by the third party's privacy policy. We will let you know when this occurs. 

**20.** If we sell some or all of our business or any assets forming part of our business, including any of our Platforms, you agree that we may transfer to the buyer your personal information. We may also disclose your personal information to potential buyers as part of any due diligence process in connection with a sale of any part of our business or business assets. 

**21.** You expressly consent to us using your personal information for all of these purposes. 

**22.** Other than as set out above or as required or permitted by law, we do not disclose your personal information we collect to third parties. That includes for the purpose of allowing third parties to direct market their products and services, unless you agree to us doing so on an "opt in" basis. 

## Credit card information

**23.** We do not collect your credit card information when you purchase a Deal. All credit card information is supplied directly by you to our merchant payment provider and is subject to its security measures and privacy policy. 

## Opting out

**24.** You may at any time through your account settings, request to "opt out" of receiving any marketing or promotional material from us and also request that we do not disclose your personal information to our Partners for direct marketing. 

**25.** If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or text message. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving "push notifications", you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app. 

**26.** If you have linked any of your social media accounts to your account with us, then you can cancel that link by changing your account settings. 

**27.** If you don't want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to enable or disable the cookie feature. If you need any assistance with changing your account settings, please contact us on our Privacy Officer. 

## Third party content

**28.** Our Platforms may contain content or advertisements from third parties (including Suppliers) and/or links to other websites. These other sites and third parties may use their own cookies and similar technologies to collect data or solicit information from you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or the content of those third party websites and platforms. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policies of any website you encounter to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. However, we do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be set by a third party on their platforms including those of our Suppliers and these terms and conditions do not cover the use of cookies by any third party. 

## Security

**29.** We are committed to protecting your personal information from unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. We store your personal information either in hard copy form or as electronic data in our IT systems. We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We maintain physical security over our hard copy and electronic data, such as locks and security systems. We also maintain computer and network security, for example, by using firewalls and other security systems such as user identifiers and passwords to control access to our computer system. We will take steps to destroy or de-identify your personal information, if we no longer require it.

## Complaints

**30.** If you wish to make a complaint about the manner in which we collect, handle, use or disclose your personal information, you may do so verbally or in writing to our Privacy Officer at the contact details above.

**31.** Our complaints process is:

  1. We will use our best endeavours to resolve your complaint within 30 days of receipt of your complaint.
  2. We will advise you of the outcome of our investigative process into your complaint including what you can do.
  3. If your complaint cannot be resolved satisfactorily within 30 days of receipt of the complaint and there is no timely prospect of the complaint being resolved, you may submit your complaint to the Australian Information Commissioner (OAIC).
  4. There will be no charges associated with handling the complaint.

## Updates

**32.** We may update this privacy policy at any time. Please refer to the date at the top of this privacy policy. If the changes affect any agreement we have with you, you may terminate the agreement by notifying us if the changes are not acceptable to you, on reasonable grounds. That may include cancelling any Deal that you have purchased and the refund of money to you, provided that occurs before you have redeemed the Deal voucher or had the Deal goods/services supplied to you.
